[ti:Bohemian Rhapsody]
[ar:Queen]
[al:]
[by:SpringPeace ZajiCzech]
[00:00]Artist: Queen
[00:00]Album : A Night At The Opera    (c)1975
[00:00]Song  : Bohemian Rhapsody     (Mercury)
[la:uk]

[00:01]Is this the real life -
[00:03]Is this just fantasy -
[00:07]Caught in a landslide -
[00:10]No escape from reality -
[00:14]Open your eyes
[00:17]Look up to the skies and see -
[00:24]I'm just a poor boy, I need no sympathy -
[00:31]Because I'm easy come, easy go,
[00:35]A little high, little low,
[00:38]Anyway the wind blows, doesn't really matter to me,
[00:47]                                             - to me -,

[00:55]Mama, just killed a man,
[01:01]Put a gun against his head,
[01:04]Pulled my trigger, now he's dead,
[01:08]Mama, life had just begun,
[01:15]But now I've gone and thrown it all away -
[01:22]Mama, ooo,
[01:29]Didn't mean to make you cry -
[01:32]If I'm not back again this time tomorrow -
[01:37]Carry on, carry on, as if nothing really matters -

[01:54]Too late, my time has come,
[02:01]Sends shivers down my spine,
[02:04]Body's aching all the time,
[02:08]Goodbye everybody - I've got to go -
[02:14]Gotta leave you all behind and face the truth -
[02:21]Mama, ooo -
[02:28]I don't want to die,
[02:32]I sometimes wish I'd never been born at all -

[03:05]I see a little silhouetto of a man,
[03:08]Scaramouche, scaramouche will you do the Fandango -
[03:12]Thunderbolt and lightning - very very frightening me -
[03:15]Galileo, Galileo,
[03:17]Galileo, Galileo
[03:19]Galileo figaro - Magnifico -
[03:22]But I'm just a poor boy and nobody loves me -
[03:25]He's just a poor boy from a poor family -
[03:28]Spare him his life from this monstrosity -
[03:33]Easy come easy go -, will you let me go -
[03:36]Bismillah! No -, we will not let you go - let him go -
[03:40]Bismillah! We will not let you go - let him go
[03:43]Bismillah! We will not let you go - let me go
[03:46]           Will not let you go - let me go
[03:48]           Will not let you go - let me go
[03:51]No, no, no, no, no, no, no -
[03:53]Mama mia, mama mia, mama mia let me go -
[03:57]Beelzebub has a devil put aside for me, for me -
[04:03]                                                 for me -

[04:15]So you think you can stone me and spit in my eye -
[04:21]So you think you can love me and leave me to die -
[04:26]Oh Baby - Can't do this to me baby -
[04:33]Just gotta get out - just gotta get right outta here -

[05:11]Nothing really matters,
[05:15]Anyone can see,
[05:18]Nothing really matters -, nothing really matters to me

[05:43]Any way the wind blows...

(Operatic Vocals - Roger, Brian and Freddie)

[offset:-500]
